A Guide to the Asia Society records FA110
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Development, 1956-1992; 13
  - General Files, 2
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Ledger Notes, 1991-1992 (Box 855, Folder 8331)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Financial Statements, 1991-1992 (Box 855, Folder 8332)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Fundraising - Posting Receipts FY 92, 1992 (Box 855, Folder 8333)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Fundraising - Batch Reports, 1988 September-December (Box 855, Folder 8334)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Budget, 1989-1990 (Box 855, Folder 8335)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Matching Gifts, 1991-1992 (Box 855, Folder 8336)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports, 1989 (Box 856, Folder 8337-8338)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - DBASE III Possibilities, 1989 (Box 856, Folder 8339)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Mr. Paul. C. Harper FY 90, 1989 (Box 856, Folder 8340)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports FY 90, 1990 May-June (Box 856, Folder 8341)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports FY 90, 1990 March-April (Box 856, Folder 8342)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports FY 90, 1990 January-February (Box 857, Folder 8343)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports FY 90, 1989 October-December (Box 857, Folder 8344)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Membership - Batch Reports FY 90, 1989 July-September (Box 857, Folder 8345)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Check Postings, 1988 (Box 857, Folder 8346)
    - Michelle Saffin Fundraising Files - Program Funding FY 90, 1990 (Box 857, Folder 8347)
  - Capital Campaign, 3
    - Certificate of Incorporation, 1956 (Box 829, Folder 7981)
    - Garun Group Capital Fund Services, 1974 (Box 829, Folder 7982)
    - Gurin Study Participants, 1974 (Box 829, Folder 7983)
    - 25th Anniversary Capital Campaign, 1978-1981 (Box 830, Folder 7984)
    - Foundation Propects 1974 - List of Attendees (Box 830, Folder 7985)
    - New Asia House Fundraising Campaign, 1974-1977 (Box 830, Folder 7986)
    - Prospects, 1975-1976 (Box 830, Folder 7987)
    - Capital Campaign 1975 - Trustee Giving (Box 830, Folder 7988)
    - Miscellaneous, 1976-1979 (Box 830, Folder 7989)
    - Gurin Group Fundraising, 1977 (Box 830, Folder 7990)
    - John D. Rockefeller Gift, 1977 (Box 831, Folder 7991)
    - Corporate Prospects, 1977 (Box 831, Folder 7992)
    - Individual Solicitation (Box 831, Folder 7993)
    - Capital Campaign Donor Lists, 1981 (Box 831, Folder 7994)
    - Individual Contributors - 1981 Capital Campaign (Box 831, Folder 7995)
    - Capital Fund - Asian Sources, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 7996)
    - Capital Campaign - Corporations, 1978 July-December (Box 831, Folder 7997)
    - Capital Campaign - Corporations, 1978 January-June (Box 831, Folder 7998)
    - George Ball, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 7999)
    - Booher, Edward E., CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8000)
    - T.J. Coolidge, Jr., Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8001)
    - G.A. Constanzo (Chairman), CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8002)
    - O.Z. Elliott, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8003)
    - Houghton Freeman, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8004)
    - David Rockefeller, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8005)
    - Maurice Greenberg, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8006)
    - Najeeb Halaby, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8007)
    - Peter Howell, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8008)
    - Antonie T. Knoppers, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8009)
    - James A. Linen, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 831, Folder 8010)
    - Robert R. Nathan, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8011)
    - Hart Perry, Campaign Solicitor, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8012)
    - Porter McKeever, 1980 (Box 831, Folder 8013)
    - Ralph A. Pfeiffer, Jr. Campaign Solicitor CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8014)
    - P. Talbot CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8015)
    - Arthur R. Taylor Campaign Solicitor CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 831, Folder 8016)
    - Marietta Tree Campaign Solicitor CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8017)
    - James M. Voss Campaign Solicitor CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8018)
    - Richard Wheeler, Campaign Solicitor, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8019)
    - Ian Wilson, Campaign Solicitor, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8020)
    - Capital Fund Campaign General, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8021)
    - Capital Campaign - Individuals, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8022)
    - Capital Campaign, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8023)
    - JDR 3rd Memorial Gifts, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8024)
    - Capital Campaign - Steering Committee, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8025)
    - Gurin Group Memos, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8026)
    - Capital Fund Campaign Plans, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8027)
    - Capital Fund Needs, 1978 (Box 832, Folder 8028)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Marietta Tree (Box 843, Folder 8224)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Robert R. Nathan (Box 843, Folder 8225)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Richard A. Fenn (Box 843, Folder 8226)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Virginia Kettering Kampf (Box 843, Folder 8227)
    - General Support 1980 - Arthur Ross (Box 843, Folder 8228)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Myron S. Falk, Jr. (Box 843, Folder 8229)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Porter McKeever (Box 843, Folder 8230)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Winthrop Munyan (Box 843, Folder 8231)
    - Richard Sherwood, CapCam Solicitor, CAPCAM 80, 1980 (Box 843, Folder 8232)
    - Richard Sneider, Capcam Solicitor, CAPCAM 80, 1980 (Box 843, Folder 8233)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - James A. Linen (Box 843, Folder 8234)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Richard A. Sherwood (Box 843, Folder 8235)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Hart Perry (Box 843, Folder 8236)
    - General Support 1980 - Ian R. Wilson (Box 843, Folder 8237)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - T.J. Coolidge, Jr. (Box 843, Folder 8238)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Ralph A. Pfeiffer, Jr. (Box 843, Folder 8239)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Datus C. Smith, Jr. (Box 843, Folder 8240)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - W. Michael Blumenthal (Box 843, Folder 8241)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Amb. Richard Sneider (Box 843, Folder 8242)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Mary Jackson Burke (Box 843, Folder 8243)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Master Lists (Box 843, Folder 8244)
    - Corporate Membership 1981 (Box 844, Folder 8245)
    - Members Miscellaneous, 1980-1982 (Box 844, Folder 8246)
    - Miscellaneous Letters and Memos, 1982 (Box 844, Folder 8247)
    - Fundraising - General, 1981 (Box 844, Folder 8248)
    - Donor Plaque, 1980-1982 (Box 844, Folder 8249)
    - 1980 Year-end Fundraising Appeal - Al Costanzo Letters to Corporate Members (Box 844, Folder 8250)
    - Helen Tucker Reception, 1980 May 28 (Box 844, Folder 8251)
    - General Support Drive 1980 - Marion Willard Johnson (Box 844, Folder 8252)
    - Arthur Ross - Trustee, 1978-1980 (Box 844, Folder 8253)
    - Asia Trip, 1980 (Box 844, Folder 8254)
    - Annual Dinner - May 13, 1980 - George W. Bal - Speaker (Box 844, Folder 8255)
    - Capital Campaign Miscellaneous, 1978-1981 (Box 844, Folder 8256)
    - Capital Fund - Asian Sources, 1981 (Box 844, Folder 8257)
    - Capital Campaign - Corporations, 1981 (Box 845, Folder 8258)
    - Capital Campaign - Reports, 1981 (Box 845, Folder 8259)
    - Capital Campaign - Contributions, 1981 (Box 845, Folder 8260)
    - Individual Prospects, 1981 (Box 845, Folder 8261)
    - Corporate Solicitation Letters, 1980 (Box 845, Folder 8262)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1982 (Box 845, Folder 8263)
    - Capital Campaign - Individuals, 1979 July-1980 (Box 845, Folder 8264)
    - Capital Fund - Asian Sources, 1979-1980 (Box 845, Folder 8265)
    - Capital Campaign - Corporations, 1979 July-1980 (Box 846, Folder 8266)
    - Capital Fund Campaign - General, 1979-1980 (Box 846, Folder 8267)
    - Capital Fund Campaign - Foundation Applications, 1979 (Box 846, Folder 8268)
    - Contributions Lists, 1969, 1979 (Box 846, Folder 8269)
    - Capital Campaign - Individual Solicitations, 1979-1981 (Box 846, Folder 8270)
    - Capital Fund Campaign - Named Gifts, 1979 (Box 846, Folder 8271)
    - Capital Campaign - Individuals, 1979 January-June (Box 846, Folder 8272)
    - Stephen Stamas, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 846, Folder 8273)
    - Groundbreaking Cermony, 1979 June 5 (Box 846, Folder 8274)
    - Capital Campaign - Corporations, 1979 January-June (Box 846, Folder 8275)
    - Individual Prospect Lists, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 857, Folder 8348)
    - Individual Prospects Original List, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8349)
    - Foundation Propect List, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 857, Folder 8350)
    - Capital Drives Cultural Organizations Reference Material, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8351)
    - Folk Art Museum Interest In Asia House (64 Park) New Asia Society Building, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 857, Folder 8352)
    - Capital Campaign - Newsletter Replies, CAPCAM 80, 1980 (Box 857, Folder 8353)
    - Newsletter Pledges CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8354)
    - Capital Campaign Newsletter Responses Volunteers CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8355)
    - Individual Receptions, CAPCAM 80, 1980 (Box 857, Folder 8356)
    - Individual Luncheon Strategies, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8357)
    - Individual Luncheons, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 857, Folder 8358)
    - Capital Drives Schools Reference Material, 1971-1980 (Box 858, Folder 8359)
    - Sample Fund Raising Letters Other Organizations, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8360)
    - Co-Chairmen for Individual Capital Campaign, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8361)
    - Solicitor's Kit (Individuals), CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8362)
    - Pledges - Sample Letter for Donor, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8363)
    - Suggestions for Solicitors, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8364)
    - Individual Donor Pledge Form, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8365)
    - Solicitation Rejections, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8366)
    - Press Conference, New Asia Society Building, CAPCAM 78, 1974 February 6 (Box 858, Folder 8367)
    - Press Conference, New Asia Society Building, CAPCAM 78, 1974 February 6 (Box 858, Folder 8368)
    - Press Conference, New Asia Society Building, CAPCAM 78, 1974 February 6 (Box 858, Folder 8369)
    - Asia Society Long Range Planning, 1967, 1975 (Box 858, Folder 8370)
    - Asia Society Trustees, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8371)
    - Additions to Donor Plaque, 1981 (Box 858, Folder 8372)
    - Capital Campaign Publicity, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8373)
    - Annual Giving Campaign Committee - Trustees, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8374)
    - Board of Trustee Prospects, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8375)
    - Trustee Pledges and Payments, CAPCAM 78 (Box 858, Folder 8376)
    - Named Gift Opportunities, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8377)
    - Quarterly payments on pledges, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8378)
    - Museum of Modern Art CAPCAM Materials (Box 858, Folder 8379)
    - Capital Campaign Brochures, CAPCAM 79, 1979 (Box 858, Folder 8380)
    - Capital Campaign - Reference Material, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 858, Folder 8381)
    - Business Committee for the Arts - Reference Materials, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8382)
    - The Economic Club of New York - Reference Materials, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8383)
    - U.S.-China Trade National Council - Reference Materials, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8384)
    - Washington Center Letter - Reference Materials, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8385)
    - American Indonesian Chamber of Commerce - Reference Materials, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8386)
    - American Australian Association - Reference Materials - (Box 859, Folder 8387)
    - Capital Campaign Fund - Transmittal Sheets, 1975-1977 (Box 859, Folder 8388)
    - Financial Statements, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8389)
    - Projected Funding - Financial Reports, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8390)
    - Coolidge-Sulpetro, 1975-1976 (Box 859, Folder 8391)
    - Building Permits, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8392)
    - Capital Campaign Expenses, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8393)
    - Capital Fund Expenses and Income, 1974-1980 (Box 859, Folder 8394)
    - Status Reports, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8395)
    - Captial Campaign Fund - Transmittal Reports, 1975-1980 (Box 859, Folder 8396)
    - Corporate Prospects Lists, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 859, Folder 8397)
    - Steering Committee Minutes, CAPCAM 78, 1978 June 28 (Box 859, Folder 8398)
    - Steering Committee and Staff Review Meetings, CAPCAM 78, 1978 February-1979 July (Box 860, Folder 8399)
    - Citibank Staff Meeting, CAPCAM 80, 1980 January 23 (Box 860, Folder 8400)
    - Solicitation Letters - Standard Top Executivee Letter, CAPCAM 78, 1978-1979 (Box 860, Folder 8401)
    - Acknowledgement Letter, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 860, Folder 8402)
    - Acknowledgement Letter - G. A. Costanzo, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 860, Folder 8403)
    - Phillips Talbot - Memoranda, CAPCAM 78, 1978-1979 (Box 860, Folder 8404)
    - Dee Ballin - Memos, CAPCAM 78, 1978-1980 (Box 860, Folder 8405)
    - General Memoranda, CAPCAM 78, 1975-1980 (Box 860, Folder 8406)
  - Asian Era Campaign, 4
    - Houston Endowment Asian Era Campaign 1985 (Box 832, Folder 8029)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Phase I, 1985 (Box 832, Folder 8030)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Asian Sources, 1985 (Box 832, Folder 8031)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Report, 1985 (Box 832, Folder 8032)
    - Korean Case Statement, 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8033)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Phase II, 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8034)
    - Asian Era Campaign - McGillicudy (Consultant), 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8035)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Miscellenaeous, 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8036)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Taiwan Pledge, 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8037)
    - Asian Era Campaign, 1986 (Box 833, Folder 8038)
    - Asian Era Campaign - Korean Support, 1986 (Box 834, Folder 8039)
    - Corporation Lists, 1982 (Box 834, Folder 8040)
    - Capital Campaign - Report, 1985 (Box 834, Folder 8041)
    - Cy Chaikin Research Group, 1983 (Box 834, Folder 8042)
    - Foundation and Corporate Prospects, 1984 (Box 834, Folder 8043)
    - Anonymous Challenge Grant - Phase II Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 834, Folder 8044)
    - Development Department Reports, 1984-1986 (Box 834, Folder 8045)
    - NEA Challenge Grant, 1986 (Box 835, Folder 8046)
    - Strategic Plan Memos, 1988 (Box 835, Folder 8047)
    - Asian Era - Korean Case Statement, 1984 (Box 835, Folder 8048)
    - Original For Xeroxing: Current Case Statement for Individuals Solicitors Kit Material, CAPCAM 78, 1978 (Box 835, Folder 8049)
    - 30th Anniversary Celebration, 1986 (Box 835, Folder 8050)
    - Ground Breaking Ceremony for New Asia House, 1979 June 5 (Box 835, Folder 8051)
  - Foundations, 5
    - Pleasant Street Foundation, 1989 (Box 835, Folder 8052)
    - Prospect Hill Foundation, Inc. (Box 835, Folder 8053)
    - William F. Ray Foundation (Box 835, Folder 8054)
    - Roblee Foundation (Box 835, Folder 8055)
    - Romill Foundation (Box 835, Folder 8056)
    - Joseph Rosen Foundation, Inc., 1990 (Box 835, Folder 8057)
    - Rudi Foundation of Indiana, Inc., 1981 (Box 835, Folder 8058)
    - Arthur M. Sackler Foundation (Box 835, Folder 8059)
    - Sasakawa Peace Foundation, 1988 (Box 835, Folder 8060)
    - S.H. and Helen R. Scheuer Family Foundation, 1989-1991 (Box 835, Folder 8061)
    - The S. and H. Foundation, 1971 (Box 835, Folder 8062)
    - The C.F. Roe Slade Foundation, 1987 (Box 835, Folder 8063)
    - Alan B. Slifka Foundation (Box 835, Folder 8064)
    - Smith Richardson Foundation, Inc., 1984 (Box 835, Folder 8065)
    - Wendy M. Sorensen Memorial Fund, 1965-1970 (Box 835, Folder 8066)
    - Speyer Foundation, 1989 (Box 835, Folder 8067)
    - The Spirit Foundation, 1984 (Box 835, Folder 8068)
    - W. Clement and Jessie V. Stone Foundation, 1969-1972 (Box 835, Folder 8069)
    - Surdna Foundation, 1984-1990 (Box 835, Folder 8070)
    - Triad Foundation, 1977 (Box 835, Folder 8071)
    - United Board For Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1983 (Box 835, Folder 8072)
    - United States Information Agency, 1988 (Box 835, Folder 8073)
    - Miriam and Ira D. Wallach Foundation, 1982-1989 (Box 835, Folder 8074)
    - Walter and Lorenz Foundation Inc. (Box 835, Folder 8075)
    - Weaterhead Foundation, 1977-1985 (Box 835, Folder 8076)
    - Frank Weedon Foundation, 1989 (Box 836, Folder 8077)
    - The Western New York Foundation, 1984 (Box 836, Folder 8078)
    - The William C. Whitney Foundation, 1965-1971 (Box 836, Folder 8079)
    - Gerald Hugh Wilkinson Memorial Fund, 1967-1970 (Box 836, Folder 8080)
    - ZBS - Foundation, 1982 (Box 836, Folder 8081)
    - Marts and Lundy, Inc., 1988-1990 (Box 836, Folder 8082)
    - Asia Era Campaign, 1984-1988 (Box 836, Folder 8083)
    - Development Plan, 1988 (Box 836, Folder 8084)
    - Foundations Survey, 1984-1986 (Box 836, Folder 8085)
    - General Prospects, 1969-1980 (Box 836, Folder 8086)
    - Asia Society Foundation - Fundraising, 1970-1980 (Box 836, Folder 8087)
    - Foundation Research, 1978-1986 (Box 836, Folder 8088)
    - Asian Literature Program (Box 837, Folder 8089)
    - Louis and Bessie Adler Foundation, Inc., 1981 (Box 837, Folder 8090)
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1982-1986 (Box 837, Folder 8091)
    - The Baird Family Fund (Formerly The Winfield Bard Foundation) (Box 837, Folder 8092)
    - The Barnes Foundation, Inc., 1984 (Box 837, Folder 8093)
    - The Beatman Foundation, 1978 (Box 837, Folder 8094)
    - Benton Foundation, 1982-1989 (Box 837, Folder 8095)
    - The George P. Bickford Foundation, 1984 (Box 837, Folder 8096)
    - Sarah Campbell Blaffer Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8097)
    - Ernestine Blakemore Trust, 1982-1987 (Box 837, Folder 8098)
    - The James G. Boswell Foundation, 1984 (Box 837, Folder 8099)
    - Breezewood Foundation - Grants, 1971-1974 (Box 837, Folder 8100)
    - Gladys Brooks Foundation, 1981 (Box 837, Folder 8101)
    - The Brown Foundation, Inc. (Box 837, Folder 8102)
    - Pearl S. Buck Foundation, 1983 (Box 837, Folder 8103)
    - Burden Foundation, 1972-1983 (Box 837, Folder 8104)
    - The Morris and Gwendlyn Caffritz Foundation (Box 837, Folder 8105)
    - Mary Flagler Cary Charitable Trust, 1980-1990 (Box 837, Folder 8106)
    - Cafritz Foundation, 1985 (Box 837, Folder 8107)
    - Edward T. and Ethelyn Chase Fund, 1981 (Box 837, Folder 8108)
    - Chio Ho Foundation (Box 837, Folder 8109)
    - Clark Foundation, 1982 (Box 837, Folder 8110)
    - Cobble Pond Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8111)
    - Coles Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8112)
    - Compton Foundation, 1985 (Box 837, Folder 8113)
    - Council On Religion and International Affairs (Box 837, Folder 8114)
    - Josephine B. Crane Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8115)
    - Culpeper Foundation, 1980-1985 (Box 837, Folder 8116)
    - Disney Foundation, 1981-1989 (Box 837, Folder 8117)
    - East-West Foundation, 1979 (Box 837, Folder 8118)
    - The Field Foundation (Box 837, Folder 8119)
    - Max. G. Fleischman Foundation, 1976 (Box 837, Folder 8120)
    - The Flagler Foundation, 1985-1989 (Box 837, Folder 8121)
    - Foundation for the Needs of Others, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8122)
    - Eugen Friedlaender, 1991 (Box 837, Folder 8123)
    - FRU Foundation, Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 837, Folder 8124)
    - Ludwig W. Frohlich Charitable Trust, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8125)
    - Alex Hillman Family Foundation (Box 837, Folder 8126)
    - Hochschild Fund, Inc., 1981 (Box 837, Folder 8127)
    - The Hewlett Foundation, 1976-1990 (Box 837, Folder 8128)
    - Herman Goldman Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 837, Folder 8129)
    - Morris Rose Goldman Foundation, 1984 (Box 837, Folder 8130)
    - Josephine H. Graeber Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8131)
    - Greentree Foundation, 1991 (Box 837, Folder 8132)
    - The Guinzburg Fund, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8133)
    - Walter and Elise Hass Fund (Box 837, Folder 8134)
    - Hartford Foundation, 1979 (Box 837, Folder 8135)
    - Jesse and Dorothy Hartman Foundation, 1980 (Box 837, Folder 8136)
    - Charles Hayden Foundation, 1982 (Box 837, Folder 8137)
    - H.J. Heinz II Charitable and Family Trust, 1982 (Box 837, Folder 8138)
    - Capezio Dance Foundation, 1984 (Box 837, Folder 8139)
    - Calder Foundation, 1980-1984 (Box 837, Folder 8140)
    - Cultural Affairs - New York City, 1981 (Box 837, Folder 8141)
    - Davis Foundation, 1983-1990 (Box 837, Folder 8142)
    - The Geraldine R. Doge Foundation, 1976-1990 (Box 838, Folder 8143)
    - Federal Council on the Arts and the Humanities, 1983 (Box 838, Folder 8144)
    - Columbia Foundation, 1990 (Box 838, Folder 8145)
    - Chiang Ching-Kuo Foundation (Box 838, Folder 8146)
    - Porothy Jordan Chadwick Fund, 1982 (Box 838, Folder 8147)
    - Owen Cheatham Foundation, 1985 (Box 838, Folder 8148)
    - Edna McConnell Clark Foundation (Box 838, Folder 8149)
    - Joseph Alexander Foundation, 1991 (Box 838, Folder 8150)
    - Howard Heinz Endowment, 1985 (Box 838, Folder 8151)
    - The George and Sadie Hyman Foundation, 1981 (Box 838, Folder 8152)
    - International Media Studios Foundation, 1985-1987 (Box 838, Folder 8153)
    - Henry M. Jackson Foundation, 1990 (Box 838, Folder 8154)
    - James Irvine Foundation (Box 838, Folder 8155)
    - Japan Center for International Exchange, 1983 (Box 838, Folder 8156)
    - Japan Economic Research Center, 1981 (Box 838, Folder 8157)
    - J.M. Foundation, 1984 (Box 838, Folder 8158)
    - Japan Expo Fund, 1980-1983 (Box 838, Folder 8159-8160)
    - Japan Fund, 1982-1990 (Box 838, Folder 8161)
    - Japan Fundraising, 1976-1977 (Box 838, Folder 8162)
    - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1980-1984 (Box 839, Folder 8163)
    - Japan-U.S. Friendship Commission, 1978-1979 (Box 839, Folder 8164)
    - Japan Expo Fund, 1978-1980 (Box 839, Folder 8165)
    - Japan World Exposition Commemorative Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 839, Folder 8166)
    - W. Alton Jones Foundation, 1990 (Box 839, Folder 8167)
    - Kampo Cultural Center, 1988 (Box 839, Folder 8168)
    - Kandell Fund, 1982 (Box 839, Folder 8169)
    - W.K. Kellogg Foundation, 1972-1983 (Box 839, Folder 8170)
    - J.F. Kennedy Foundation, 1982 (Box 839, Folder 8171)
    - Korean-American Association, 1979 (Box 839, Folder 8172)
    - The Kulchur Foundation, 1988 (Box 839, Folder 8173)
    - Lan Ting Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8174)
    - Robert Lehman Foundation, Inc. (Box 839, Folder 8175)
    - The Bertha Drabkin Goodwin Leviton Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8176)
    - Frances and John L. Loeb Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8177)
    - Richard Lounsberty Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8178)
    - The Joseph Love Foundation, Inc. (Box 839, Folder 8179)
    - Josiah Macy, Jr., Foundation, 1979 (Box 839, Folder 8180)
    - Maguire Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8181)
    - Marble Fund (Box 839, Folder 8182)
    - Markle Foundation, 1973-1979 (Box 839, Folder 8183)
    - German Marshall Fund of the U.S., 1974-1975 (Box 839, Folder 8184)
    - McKnight Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8185)
    - Mertz-Gilmore Foundation, 1981 (Box 839, Folder 8186)
    - The Berger-Mittleman Family Foundation (Box 839, Folder 8187)
    - Charles Stewart Mott Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 839, Folder 8188)
    - Musser Endowment for International Peace (Box 839, Folder 8189)
    - New York Foundation, 1971-1973 (Box 839, Folder 8190)
    - New-Land Foundation, 1991 (Box 839, Folder 8191)